Every generation needs a new revolution
Itty Bitty Titty Committee is a comedy film directed by Jamie Babbit.
High School grad and all American gal, Anna, finds her purpose and herself after she
hooks up with the radical feminists in The Itty Bitty Titty Committee.
Anna, played by Melonie Díaz.
Sadie, played by Nicole Vicius.
Calvin, played by Daniel Sea.
Meat, played by Deak Evgenikos.
Aggie, played by Lauren Mollica.
Marcy Maloney, played by Guinevere Turner.
Itty Bitty Titty Committee is a 2007 American
comedy film directed by Jamie Babbit.
It follows the political awakening of Anna, a young, mild-mannered
lesbian woman who joins a radical feminist group.
The film is produced by non-profit organization POWER UP.
Itty Bitty Titty Committee had its world premiere at the film festival Berlinale on
February 9, 2007, where it was nominated for a Teddy Award for Best Feature.
It had its American premiere at South by Southwest (SXSW) in March
2007, where it won the Jury Prize for Best Feature.
The film was theatrically released on September 28, 2007.
The film explores themes of beauty, surgeon,
plastic surgery, lgbt, woman director.
The tone is lighthearted.